原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
翻譯     蘇葵  1.0  Tong大梨
翻譯     小酸奶  哈里不是波特  白夜君
校對     小酸奶
時間軸     念念  無關風粵  西·查
后期     吉吉
總監     小酸奶
深入黑暗  第一季 第十一集
開學前一天
真不敢相信我要這么做
I can't believe I'm doing this.
誰畢業了還闖回學校里去
Who graduates and then breaks back into the school?
你最好別臨陣脫逃
You better not be backing out.
我在這監獄里還要蹲一年呢
I still have one more year left in this prison.
給我點光
Give me a light.
哥們  他們可能換了鎖了
Dude, they might have changed the locks, man.
我們做的事真的違法嗎
Is what we're doing actually illegal?
我不知道  反正肯定不好
I don't know, I mean, it's definitely not good.
要我老實說的話
I kind of think you're a fucking creep
我覺得你挺恐怖的
if you want me to be honest.
我們去拿梯子吧
Let's just get the ladder.
上將隊  真俗氣
The Admirals. How corny.
赫布魯克
我們怎么不叫老虎隊  毒蛇隊
We could have been the tigers or the vipers.
你確定沒有校園保安嗎
Are you sure there's no one campus security?
確定  哥們
Yeah, dude, I'm sure.
這破地方連廁紙都買不起
This place can't even afford toilet paper.
女生更衣室
好吧
All right.
就在上面
Right up there.
好
All right.
如果你需要的話  我有螺絲刀
I got a screwdriver if you need it.
我在這里時
You know, I always thought
總覺得有什么在監視我們
something was watching us when I was here.
好吧
All right.
手機上能看到了嗎
You see it on your phone?
我去  成功了
Holy shit, it works.
哥們  這絕對是違法的
Dude, this is definitely illegal.
我可不會像個變態似的
I'm not gonna be a pervert about it.
反正這里的女生都很丑
The girls are ugly here anyway.
我只會在返校前進行直播
I'm just gonna livestream it before homecoming,
讓大家慌張
everyone's gonna freak out,
這樣一整個學年都會很好玩
and the whole school year's gonna be fun.
好吧  我來安完
All right, I'll secure it.
"我可不會像個變態似的"
"I'm not gonna be a pervert about it."
你什么毛病
What's wrong with you?
瘋子
Crazy.
陶德
Todd.
Todd?
陶德
Todd!
陶德  這可不好玩  別鬧了
Todd, this isn't funny. Quit it.
搞什么
What the fuck?
該死
Oh, shit!
校鬼
早上好  赫布魯克高中
Good morning, Helbrook High.
各位上將們  歡迎回到學校
Fellow Admirals, welcome back to school.
我是艾瑞卡·楊  高四班長
I'm Erica Yang, your Senior Class President.
我想首先向各位高四生
I'd like to start with a special message
傳達一條特別信息
for my fellow seniors.
各位  這是我們最后同校的一年了
Guys, this will be our final year together.
誰知道之后我們會有怎樣的際遇
After this, who knows what will happen?
我們可能再也見不到彼此了
We may never see each other again.
有時我會想  時間都去哪了啊
Sometimes I think, whoa, where did these years go?
我一直在學習
All I did was study...
所以我們盡量抓住這最后一年吧
So let's make the best of our last year.
去冒險  去認識那個
Take a risk, get to know that person
你一直好奇的人
you've always been curious about
趁還來得及去實現你的大計劃
and follow through on your big plans before it's too late.
但此外  提前大學申請
But also, early college applications
11月結束
are due in November.
我們做個強勢收尾吧
Let's finish strong.
加油上將們
Go Admirals!
星期六
一周后
該死
Fuck.
Shit.
艾瑞卡
Erica!
Erica.
-杰森  -上不夠學啊
- Jason. - Just can't get enough of school, huh?
還是在跟蹤我
Or are you stalking me?
你居然這么說  明明是你來找我的
Funny you should say that 'cause I think you came to me.
你態度怎么這樣
Hey, what's with the attitude?
是你跟我分手的  記得嗎
You broke up with me, remember?
是啊  但你高二時跟我分手的
Yeah, well, you broke up with me sophomore year,
所以我大概是記仇
so, I guess I hold a grudge.
我知道你今年結束后
Look, I know after this year
大概會去哈佛大學
you're probably going off to Harvard
我就再也見不到你了
and I'll never see you again,
但我們現在能好好的嗎
but for now can we just be nice?
如果我當初很混蛋那抱歉了
I'm sorry if I was a jerk.
好吧
Okay.
好嗎
Okay?
你可以不再躲我了嗎
So you can stop ghosting me?
好啊  但你要害我遲到了
Sure, but you're gonna make me late.
遲什么到  你還有周末留堂嗎
Late for what? You got weekend detention or something?
不會吧
No fuckin' way.
真的假的
Seriously?
艾瑞卡·楊會是做了什么呢
What could Erica Yang have possibly done?
別告訴別人  好嗎
Hey, don't tell anyone, okay?
這事可能要瘋傳的
This may go viral.
我說真的
I'm serious.
你不能告訴任何人我今天留堂了
You can't tell anyone I had detention today.
走著瞧吧
We'll see.
或許等會兒我們去約會時你可以告訴我你做了什么
Maybe you can tell me what you did on our date later.
隨便吧
Whatever.
我死了
I died.
我知道
I know.
大概得在場才會覺得好笑
I guess you had to be there.
我更快  更強
I'm faster, I'm stronger.
我體力上并不更強
I mean, I'm not physically stronger,
但我...
but like I'm like, um...
看那是誰
Look who it is.
那不是學校的完美公主小姐嗎
Isn't that the Princess Miss Perfect of the school?
她要跟我們一起留堂
Is she having detention with us?
你不能坐那里
Hey, you can't sit there.
那是我的座位
It's my seat.
那是她的
That one's hers.
你迷路了嗎
Are you lost?
你知道這是留堂吧
You know this is detention, right?
我知道
I'm aware.
你幾乎什么都說錯了
You're wrong about like almost everything.
看看誰回來了
Hey, look who's back.
你們好啊
Hi, guys.
學年第一個周末
First weekend of the school year?
厲害了
I am impressed.
閉嘴  看前面
Mouths shut, eyes up.
都就坐
Everybody take a seat.
歡迎來到今年第一次周六留堂
Welcome to the first Saturday detention of the year.
我是副校長  阿姆斯特朗老師
I am your Vice Principal, Mr. Armstrong.
你們清楚規矩
You know the drill.
手機放進桶里
Phones in the bucket.
請報出全名以確認出席
Please give me your full name for attendance.
麗莎·惠特莫爾
Lizzy Whitmore.
早  阿姆斯特朗老師
Morning, Mr. Armstrong.
伊麗莎白  你還是屢教不改
Elizabeth, I see you're still incorrigible.
什么
Incorrial what?
拉塞爾·瓊斯  阿姆斯特朗老師  你好嗎
Russel Jones, Mr. Armstrong, how are you?
夠了
That's enough.
名字就行
The name will do.
你已經知道我的名字了  寫下來就行
You already know my name, just write it down.
你這就要找我麻煩嗎
Are you messing with me already,
你個小混蛋
you little prick?
我覺得你是不能那么喊我的
I don't think you're allowed to call me that.
這有違規定
It's against the rules.
留堂的孩子還教訓我規矩的事
I got kids in detention telling me about the rules.
我跟你說清楚  維克多
I'm gonna make something really clear for you, Victor.
才沒人在乎你呢
Nobody gives a flying monkey turd about you.
我對你這種差生想說什么做什么都行
I say and do whatever I want to delinquents like you.
所以  報上姓名
So, say your name.
維克多·卡斯特羅
Victor Castro.
看
See?
沒那么難吧
That wasn't so hard.
布雷特·卡勒維
Brett Callaway.
我沒帶我的手機  老師
Oh, I don't have mine, sir.
你在騙我嗎
Are you messing with me?
你們這些孩子
You kids can't go two minutes
兩分鐘不看手機都做不到
without looking at one of these things.
這是種病
It's a disease.
我記得不讓帶手機
I remembered that phones aren't allowed
我就沒帶來  真的
so I didn't bring mine, honest.
如果我發現你在撒謊
If I find out you're lying to me,
我就停你的學  明白嗎
I'm gonna suspend you, you understand?
是  老師
Yes, sir.
你是個好孩子
You're a nice kid.
我不希望你再回來
I don't want to see you back again
跟這些白癡作伴
with these idiots.
-好吧  -拜托  我干什么了
- Okay. - Come on, what did I do?
最后同等重要的
And last but not least,
我們今天的特別來賓
our very, very special guest for the day,
艾瑞卡·楊小姐
Ms. Erica Yang.
很不幸要參加周末的留堂
Who lucked out with weekend detention
因為她那可恥的罪行
after her shameful, shameful crime.
天哪  她干什么了
Whoa, what did she do?
不關你們的事
Hey, that's nobody else's business.
-好吧  -我不能留著手機嗎
- Okay. - I can't keep my phone?
不  你不能留著手機
No, you can't keep your phone.
你正留堂呢  規矩不同了
You're in detention now, things are different here.
我得說你非常非常幸運
You know, I have to say that you're very, very lucky
摩根校長希望你這樣的年輕姑娘成功
that Principal Morgan wants young ladies like you to succeed
因為要換了我  你就被開除了
because if it were up to me you would have been expelled.
我會用你殺雞儆猴
I would have made an example out of you.
那是什么
What's this?
我想做些作業
I was going to do some homework.
這不是自習室
This isn't study hall.
他會讓我們寫檢討  反省自己有多糟糕
He's gonna make us write essays about how awful we are.
又錯了  伊麗莎白
Wrong again, Elizabeth,
因為顯然這沒屁用
since clearly it doesn't do shit.
從今天起
As of today,
在我監督留堂時
when you're in my detention...
你們要打掃學校
...you get to clean the school.
非常感謝
Hi, yes, thank you so much.
你不能讓我們干雜活
You can't make us do chores.
我能  是的  我能
Oh, yes, I can, yes, I can.
項目清單第一項
The first order of business
你們要除掉
is that you're going to be removing
這些桌子下面的
all of the gum from the undersides
所有口香糖
of all of these tables.
太惡心了
That's disgusting.
是的  是的  是很惡心
Yes! Yes, it is disgusting.
所以麻煩不要把你們口香糖隨便亂粘
So please don't stick your gum on things.
生命的循環
Circle of life.
還有  如果你們用漂白劑
Also, if you'd like to use this bleach,
你們也可以除掉
you can remove some of the graffiti
桌底下的一些涂鴉
that's under the tables as well.
這是違法的
This is illegal.
我不干
I'm not doing this.
會的  你會的
Oh, yes, you are.
你要欣欣然上來
You're gonna dance on up here,
拿一個工具
you're gonna grab one of those,
然后去干活
and you're gonna get to work.
你能把我怎樣
Make me.
老兄  算了吧
Dude, just let it go.
有人跟你說話了嗎
Was anyone talking to you?
我不知道這有什么誤會
I don't know what the confusion here is.
這里我負責  我下命令  你們都聽我的
I'm in charge and when I give you an order, you listen.
就像你求你妻子
Like how your wife listened
別離開時她聽你的嗎
when you begged her not to leave you?
不好意思  你的前妻
I'm sorry, your ex-wife.
大伙兒  別動手
You guys, please.
是啊  是啊  沒事
Yeah, yeah, that's fine.
沒關系  你說得對
That's fine, yeah, you're right.
你說得對  你說得對
You're right, you're right.
我是副校長  我不該碰你
I'm the Vice Principal, I shouldn't be touching you.
我就再給你四個周六
I'll just give you four more Saturdays.
-干什么  -什么
- For what? - What's that?
什么  你想要八個
What's that? You want eight?
因為  因為就那么簡單
Because-because it's just that easy.
我只需要寫出來
All I have to do is write it out
讓你承受后果
and then you suffer the consequences.
如果你想做個混蛋
If you want to be a fuckup...
那我成全你
...I'm here to support you.
很好
Good.
大伙兒都干活
Everybody get to work.
我現在沒心情
Not in the mood.
好了
All right, uh,
我要去辦公室回些郵件
I'm gonna go to my office and work on some emails.
有誰敢離開這里  就被停學
Anybody who leaves this room is suspended.
因為那兩個失蹤的孩子  我們還在封鎖中
We're still on lockdown because of those two missing kids,
所以我很不幸要對你們的安全負責
so unfortunately for me I am responsible for you,
但我想這不意味著
but I trust that that doesn't mean
我要每時每刻盯著你們
that I have to babysit you the entire time.
對嗎
Right?
對  阿姆斯特朗老師
Yes, Mr. Armstrong.
老天  我以為他永遠不走呢
God, I thought he'd never leave.
今天他比平時待得更久
Took longer than he usually does.
真不敢相信陶德還失蹤著
I can't believe Todd is still missing.
我信  那家伙是個白癡
I can, that guy's an idiot.
他不在感覺怪怪的
Feels weird without him.
有多久了
How long has it been?
年初開始吧  我想
Since the beginning of the year, I think.
也許他被那個鬼抓了
Maybe the ghost got him.
我的天  別再說這個了
Oh, my god, please do not start with that.
我一直告訴別人
I keep trying to tell people.
赫布魯克鬧鬼
Helbrook is haunted.
你不會真相信吧
You don't actually believe that, do you?
信啊  如果我信呢
Yeah, what if I did?
你告訴我
You tell me.
為什么學校每年都有學生失蹤
Why do students go missing every year?
校鬼把他們抓走了
The School Spirit comes and takes them away.
你聽說過  對吧
You heard about that, right?
我聽過傳說
I mean, yeah, I've heard stories,
但我一直以為是個玩笑
but I always just assumed it was a joke.
如果真有人失蹤就不算是玩笑了
It's not a joke if people are actually disappearing.
反正你不用擔心
Well, you don't have to worry.
為什么
Why is that?
傳說不是說那鬼只抓壞孩子嗎
I mean, isn't the legend like the ghost only takes bad kids?
那我們都死定了
Well, then we're all dead.
你什么意思  壞孩子
What did you mean, uh, bad kids though?
多壞算壞
Like how bad?
我聽說是個穿上將衣服的老女人
I heard it's an old lady in an Admiral costume,
她只抓男孩  好強奸他們
and she only takes boys so she can rape them.
這太蠢了
That is so stupid.
什么意思  強壯  性欲旺盛的
What do you mean, like, a strong old woman
老女人嗎
who's really horny?
就像是個死了的僵尸女士
It's like a dead zombie lady.
她是十多年前學校的一位緊張兮兮的老師
Apparently, she was some uptight teacher from like 10 years ago.
學生們對她使了個惡作劇
The kids pulled a prank on her.
他們倒了一盆涼水在她身上
They dumped a bunch of cold water on her.
具體怎么回事也不清楚
Nobody knows exactly.
但她突發心臟病  當場就死了
But she had a heart attack and died right there on the spot.
那些學生怕極了  于是用
The kids freaked out, so they covered her up
上將的吉祥物服裝將她掩蓋
by putting her in an Admiral mascot costume
然后把尸體藏在了學校里
and hid her body on campus.
從那以后  她就一直在學校陰魂不散
And since then, she's been haunting the school
向壞孩子報仇
and taking revenge on bad kids.
說到壞
Speaking of bad,
剛才他說的"你沒被開除已經很走運了"是怎么回事
what was all that "You're lucky to not be expelled" talk?
你干什么了
What'd you do?
我不太想說
I really prefer not to talk about it.
你擔心我們會評頭論足嗎
Are you worried we're gonna judge you?
你不說我們會越加評頭論足
We'll judge you more for not telling.
我覺得大家都有點感興趣
I think we're all a little intrigued.
我打賭她什么也沒做
I bet she didn't do anything.
是嗎
Yeah, right?
她也許是被派來打我們幾個小報告的
She's probably here to write some report on us fuckups.
你就扯吧  好嗎
Speak for yourself, okay?
我打算拿到A和B呢
I plan to get all As and Bs.
是真的嗎  你是來作業做研究的
Is that true? Are you just here doing research?
你們為什么都這么好奇
Why are you all so curious?
你做了什么讓你留堂
What did you do to get detention?
該問我沒做什么
What didn't I do?
喝酒  抽煙
Drinking, smoking.
違抗命令
Insubordination.
你聽上去很自豪
You sound like you're proud.
我只是好好享受生活
I'm just living my best life.
我們不是所有人都想上哈佛
Not all of us want to go to Harvard.
她故意留堂  這樣就不用回家
She gets detention on purpose so she doesn't have to go home
面對她那酒鬼媽媽了
and be with her alcoholic mom.
-去你的  -得了吧
- Screw you. - Oh, please.
不如我們回去干活吧
Why don't we just get back to work?
阿姆斯特朗老師隨時可能回來
Mr. Armstrong might come back any minute.
親愛的  不會的
Oh, sweetie, no.
他要離開好一會
He'll be gone for a while.
你們怎么知道
How do you know that?
是真的
No, it's true.
他正在自己辦公室喝酒呢
He's in his office right now getting drunk.
-連他都知道  -什么
- Even he knows. - What?
阿姆斯特朗是酒鬼
Armstrong's an alcoholic.
我就不能離開它們
I just can't get away from them.
說到這個
Speaking of which,
拉斯  你能再給我們來點那酒嗎
hey, Russ, can you get us that booze again?
-我該嗎  -當然
- Should I? - Yeah.
可以調節下這兒的氣氛
The vibe in here could use a little help.
你的儲物柜還有大麻嗎
still got that weed in your locker?
一直有
Always.
大伙  阿姆斯特朗老師今天看起來情緒不好
You guys, Mr. Armstrong seems pretty tense today.
也許我們該悠著點
Maybe we should just take it easy.
老兄  拜托  你總是掃興
Dude, come on, you're always such a buzzkill.
艾瑞卡
Erica...
你現在是我們中的一員了
You're one of us now.
你馬上就要開始了
You're about to get initiated.
沒錯
Fuck yeah.
我們先讓她嗨起來
We'll get her lit.
然后她就會告訴我們為什么來這了
Then she can tell us why she's here.
這些人太魯莽了
Those guys are so reckless.
你來這里后他們更猖狂了
They're even worse when you're here.
我理解
I get it.
大家都認為我是最棒的學生
Everyone thinks I'm this perfect student.
你就是啊
Well, you are.
其實我很驚訝我竟然
I'm actually really amazed that I'm speaking
現在正在和艾瑞卡·楊聊天
with the Erica Yang right now.
拜托
Please.
兩次獲得"年度最佳學生"
Yeah, two Time Admiral of the Year.
平均分最高  資深班長
Highest GPA, senior class president.
你是赫布魯克的黃金標準
You're the gold standard at Helbrook.
我并不知道這些
I don't know about that.
你的演講棒極了
And your speech was incredible.
我的演講
My speech?
是的  就在年初的時候
Yeah, at the beginning of the year.
非常振奮人心  我一直記在心上
It was inspiring, I really took it to heart.
你曾說  這是最后一年了  要勇于冒險
You know, about it being the last year and taking risks
不要留下遺憾
and not having regrets.
這也正是我來這里的原因
It's actually the reason why I'm here right now.
不  你干了什么
Oh, no, what'd you do?
其實無所謂
Actually, never mind.
我問你的語氣就像他們問我一樣
Now I'm doing to you what they were doing to me.
我很驚訝能在這里看到你
I was really surprised to see you here.
阿姆斯特朗老師說你差點被開除
Mr. Armstrong said that you almost got expelled.
這看起來是不可能的事
It just seems impossible.
他是認真的還是...
Was he being serious or was it...?
該死...
Oh, mother...?
你沒事吧
Are you okay?
老天  今天遭透了
Man, this day sucks.
或許我們應該和他們一起喝醉
Maybe we should just get drunk with them.
我去給你拿急救箱
I'll go get you a first aid kit.
我覺得木工房里有一個
I think there's one in woodshop.
我馬上回來
I'll be right back.
你一個人在這沒事吧
Are you gonna be okay in here by yourself?
當然沒事
Yeah, of course.
好的
Okay.
鱷梨煙斗還是電子煙
Okay, so, avocado pipe or vape?
無所謂  我只想再來杯蘇格蘭酒
I don't care, I just want that scotch again.
還是叫威士忌  等等  這倆有什么區別
Or is it whiskey? Wait, what's the difference?
都是酒鬼們的最愛
All alcoholics.
校訓在我們頭上[校鬼在看著我們]
Hm, the School Spirit is upon us.
-我討厭你  -你們倆去拿酒
- I hate you. - You guys get the booze
我們一會在這里集合
and we'll meet back here?
等等  你要去哪里
Wait, where are you going?
你別擔心了
Don't worry about it.
怎么  你是無敵的
What, so you're invincible?
不會陷入麻煩嗎
You just can't get in trouble?
我要去拉屎
I need to take a shit.
這我就無話可說了
Can't argue with that.
-和以前一樣嗎  -是的  我來檢查一下
- Same as before? - Yeah, let me check.
好的
Okay.
好  別拿那些好的
Okay, don't get the good stuff.
他會注意到的  和我媽一樣
He'll notice that, it's the same as my mom.
她經常喝的酒不見的話
Like when the stuff she gets all the time is gone,
她只是認為她給喝了
she just assumes that she drank it.
好的
Oh... okay.
阿姆斯特朗老師
貝弗莉·阿姆斯特朗
我的天...
Oh, my go...
拉斯
Russ?
小維
Vic?
我只能找到一些邦迪創可貼
Hey, I can only find a few BandAids.
我覺得已經止住了
I think it coagulated.
我能看一眼嗎
Oh, can I take a look?
當然
Sure.
你們為什么拉著手
Were you guys holding hands?
你不是在和籃球隊的那個人談戀愛嗎
Aren't you with that guy from the basketball team?
不  其實我們分手了
No, actually we broke up.
我知道了
Oh, I see.
你們為什么不明白
Oh, what don't you guys understand
我們是在你的儲物柜前集合
about meet back at your locker?
我像個傻子一樣在那里等著
I was waiting there like a dumbass.
拉斯呢
Where's Russ?
我不知道
I don't know.
我沒看見他
I didn't see him.
沒有  他沒回到過這里
Yeah, no, he didn't come back here.
糟了
Shit.
你們覺得他不會被抓吧
You don't think he got caught, do you?
不會  如果他被抓了
No, Armstrong would be in here
阿姆斯特朗會回到這里  像個瘋子一樣大喊
screaming like a maniac if he did.
所以你想抽電子煙
So, uh, do you want to hit the vape
還是你也決定變成一個酒鬼
or are you determined to become an alcoholic too?
如果我不喝酒  你會更開心嗎
Would it make you happier if I didn't drink?
會的
Yes.
那我們抽電子煙吧
Then let's just hit the vape.
好
All right.
你們一起來嗎
Are you two down?
我不覺得這是個好主意
I don't think this is a good idea.
我的天  你覺得任何事都是個壞主意
Oh, my god, you think everything is a bad idea.
如果阿姆斯特朗老師突然出現呢
Yeah, what if Mr. Armstrong surprises us?
他不會的  他根本不在乎我們
He won't, he doesn't care enough to.
等等  等一下
Wait, hold up.
你們兩個要去告密嗎
Are you two going to snitch?
不  我不告密
No, I don't snitch.
我不會說的
I won't tell.
我不知道是否該相信他們
I don't know if I trust 'em.
你們中的一個人要和我們一起抽
One of you needs to do this with us,
這樣我們才能知道你們不是"緝毒警"
so we know you guys aren't narcs.
我不能抽煙  真的
I can't use that stuff, really.
那只能是你了
Well, then it's gotta be you.
你以前磕嗨過嗎
Have you been high before?
她當然沒有過
Of course she hasn't.
-你可不知道  -好
- You don't know that. - All right,
那你就抽一個
well then hit it.
證明一下你不是警察
Prove that you're not a cop.
如果你們想抽  我們不會打小報告
If you want to do it, we won't tell,
但別強迫艾瑞卡抽
but just don't make Erica do it.
沒人強迫我做任何事
No one makes me do anything.
真棒  女性的力量  我喜歡
Fuck yeah, woman power, I like that.
讓我看看
Let me see it.
-我應該怎么做  -你只需要
- What do I do? - You just hold down
按著這個按鈕  然后吸氣
that button and inhale.
等等  我們來做個交易
Wait, let's make a deal.
如果我抽了  證明我不是"緝毒警"之類的
If I do this and prove that I'm not a narc or whatever,
你們就絕對不能告訴別人
then you guys absolutely can't tell anyone
我今天來過這里
that I was here today at all.
-好  -沒問題
- Yeah. - That's fine.
留堂期間發生的事就封存在這間圖書館里
What happens in detention stays in detention.
-保證  -我保證
- Promise. - I promise.
老天啊  我們要和艾瑞卡·楊一起嗑藥了
Holy shit, we're about to get high with Erica Yang.
太壯觀了
Epic.
他們以為我在社區服務
They think I have community service.
你確實藏了許多秘密
You really do keep a lot of secrets.
所以呢
So what?
你父母不讓你吃晚飯嗎
Your parents wouldn't let you eat dinner?
不讓
Nope.
除非我把所有作業都寫完
Not until I finished all my homework
而且要通過他們編的測試題
and passed their madeup prep quiz.
這太扯了
That's crazy.
我爸只會看體育比賽
All my dad does is watch sports.
我媽只會在他看比賽的時候  給他吃的
And all my mom does is feed him while he's doing it.
至少他們不管你
At least they leave you alone.
沒錯  但他們是失敗者
Yeah, but they're fucking losers.
這不意味著你也要當失敗者
Doesn't mean you have to be one.
你管我叫失敗者嗎
Are you calling me a loser?
什么  沒有
What? No.
我只是說  我們可以走自己的路
No, I was... was just saying we can make our own path.
我們可以選擇當贏家
You know, we can choose to be winners.
謝謝  兄弟
Thanks, buddy.
我已經知道了
I already know.
我上完高中之后
I'm gonna be a firefighter
我想去當一名消防員
when I'm done with this high school nonsense.
你知道嗎
You know what?
你不賴嘛  艾瑞卡·楊
You're not so bad, Erica Yang.
謝謝你
Thank you. I think.
我以為你就是個無聊的人
I thought you were this total square,
但怎么說呢  你自己至少知道這點
but like at least you're aware of it.
這是什么意思
What does that even mean?
意思是這不是她的錯
Like it's not her fault
她身上的壓力太大了
she's got all this pressure on her.
你懂什么壓力
What do you know about pressure?
我當然了解壓力
Hey, I know about pressure.
我們都有各種壓力
We all have pressure to be something.
所以  你到底干了什么  差點被開除
So, what did you do to almost get expelled?
我還是不告訴你們
I'm still not telling you guys.
該死  你在開玩笑嗎
Dammit, are you kidding?
真的不是什么很棒或者很有意思的事
It's really not something cool or interesting.
我也不有趣  也不棒
I'm not interesting or cool.
我周三很無聊  就拉響了防火警報
I got bored on Wednesday, so I pulled the fire alarm.
拉響防火警報很嚴重的
Pulling the fire alarm is kind of a serious thing.
我同意
I agree.
好吧  隨便了
All right, whatever.
我們那天因為這個而取消了一場測試
You know, we had to miss a test that day because of it.
-好吧  -謝謝你
- Okay. - Thank you.
不客氣
You are welcome.
你們應該把門打開
Eh, you guys should open the door.
好吧  我去
All right, I'll do it.
我來吧
I got this.
我們相信你
We believe in you.
你抽過大麻嗎
Have you ever smoked weed?
沒有
No.
-沒有  -你現在可能算接觸性吸毒了
- No. - You could be a little contact high right now.
-你得開心點  -我們得腐化他
- You need to lighten up. - We should corrupt him.
我覺得你們應該不要再對我指手畫腳
I think you should stop telling me what to do.
就是放松一下
It just takes the edge off, you know?
你們覺得你們的朋友去哪里了
Where do you think your friend went?
對了  拉斯
Oh yeah, Russ, uh...
我不知道
I don't know.
那笨蛋可能跑了
That dumbass probably ditched.
所以他才會被留堂
It's why he's in detention in the first place.
你沒事吧
Hey, are you okay?
你看上去  你看上去很擔心
You look...You look worried.
不  我只是
No, I'm just...
勁過了
Faded.
我只是在想校鬼的事
I was just thinking about the School Spirit.
天啊  哥們  看把孩子嚇成什么樣了
Oh, Jesus, come on, dude, look what you've done to her.
-等等  -好吧
- Wait, shh! - Okay.
你們聽到了嗎
Do you hear that?
她完全飄了
Dude, she's tripping.
好吧  現在你們真的嚇到我了
Okay, come on, now you guys are gonna freak me out.
-阿姆斯特朗  -該死
- Armstrong! - Fuck!
-你們能聞出來嗎  -我分辨不出來
- Can you smell it? - I can't tell.
真不知道你們為什么每次都選味道沖的
I don't know why you guys always get the scented ones.
這絕對能聞出來
You can definitely smell it.
該死
Oh, shoot.
怎么回事
What is going on here?
這門為什么開著
Why is this door open?
我們正打算用漂白劑清理桌子
We were just about to clean the desks with bleach
結果被我不小心弄掉在地上了
and then I accidentally dropped it.
別別別用手來收拾
Now, don't...don't...don't clean it with your hands,
這東西有毒
this stuff is toxic.
你們得拿個拖把和...
Now you need to get a mop and a...
和一個桶
and a bucket.
拖把和桶在哪里
Uh, where is the mop and the bucket?
是不是在門衛室
Is it in the janitor's closet?
等一下  等一下  不要動
Wait, wait, freeze, freeze.
你們在這里抽大麻嗎
Are you guys smoking in here?
你這是想要掩蓋嗎
Is this you trying to cover this up?
對不起
I'm sorry.
我只是覺得
It's just so funny,
我們會在留堂期間
the idea that we'd be smoking
抽大麻的想法太好笑了
while we're in detention?
你
You.
他們在抽大麻嗎
Are they smoking?
我覺得你聞到的是漂白劑的味道  先生
I think what you're smelling is the bleach, sir.
不然就是酒味
That or alcohol.
我覺得我好像聞到了酒味
I feel like I smell alcohol,
但我們都沒有喝酒
but we haven't been drinking.
你說什么
What did you say?
我不知道  我聞到了
I don't know, I smell it.
好吧
All right.
你們去門衛室拿桶來
You get the bucket from the janitor's closet
-把這里清理干凈  -好的  阿姆斯特朗老師
- and clean this up. - Yes, Mr. Armstrong.
等一下
Wait a minute.
-拉塞爾在哪里  -你沒有見到他嗎
- Where's Russel? - You haven't seen him?
我為什么會見到他
Why would I have seen him?
-他跑哪里去了  -我覺得
- Where the hell is he? - I mean, I...
我覺得可以說他跑了
I think it's safe to say he ditched.
什么
What?
我說了學校封鎖了
I told you guys we're on lockdown.
我根本無法信任你們這些廢物
I'm just gonna have to literally lock the building doors
能干好一件事  所以我必須
since I can't trust any of you twerps
真的把每扇門都給鎖上
to do a single goddamn thing.
該死
Fuck!
趕緊收拾干凈
Clean this up.
真是太厲害了
That was awesome.
-謝了  -天啊
- Thanks. - Oh, my god.
哥們  真不敢相信你真的那么說了
Dude, I cannot believe you said that.
你看到他臉上的表情了嗎
Did you see the look on his face?
他完全慫了
He totally backed down.
當然了
Of course he did.
好了  哥們  你不是警察了
All right, dude, you're not a cop.
謝謝你  真的
Thank you. Really.
不然我肯定會有大麻煩的
I would have been in so much trouble.
看吧  我就說我不會告密的
See, I told you guys I wasn't a snitch,
但是剛剛真的差點就被識破了
but did you see how close that was?
走吧  我們去拿拖把
Come on, let's go get the mop.
好吧
Okay.
Ooh, okay.
你們倆在學校里不許愛愛哦
Hey, you two, no sex on campus.
校鬼會來抓你們的
The School Spirit will come and get you.
成熟點
Grow up.
高四規矩
我覺得我好像在慢慢地回流
I feel like I'm slowly doing a backflip.
真不敢相信我嗑嗨了
I can't believe I'm stoned.
布雷特  我們不能告訴任何人
Brett, we can't tell anybody about this.
我不會的
I won't.
但你不要再讓那些人
You really have to stop letting those guys
逼你做那些不是你會做的事
pressure you into doing things that aren't you.
他們也沒有那么壞
They're not so bad.
他們不是好學生
I mean, they're not great students,
但他們也不是壞人
but they're not bad people.
嗯
Yeah.
我們是不是一起上過課
Have we had a class together?
嗯  我們...我們一起上過課
Um, yeah, we've...We had class, um,
但我比較喜歡做人群中的一個路人甲
but I kind of just like to stay in the background.
我明白
I get that.
有時候我也會希望我是個無名小卒
Sometimes I wish I was a nobody.
不要那么說
Don't say that.
很多人都很崇拜你
A lot of people look up to you.
或者說應該崇拜你
Or they should.
也許我們不該嗑嗨
Maybe we shouldn't have gotten high
然后講鬼故事
and told ghost stories.
這世上沒有鬼
There's no such thing as ghosts.
我都分不清是我嗑嗨了還是真的聽到什么了
I can't tell if I'm high or if I'm hearing things.
你肯定會聽到些什么的
You're definitely just hearing things.
這幢樓有年頭了
It's an old building.
天啊
Oh, my god!
杰森  你嚇了我一大跳
Jason, you scared the shit out of me.
太好了  我就想嚇你呢
Great, that was the point.
你好
Sup.
你們在干什么
What are you guys doing?
你不是在留堂嗎
I thought you had detention?
是的
Oh, we do.
我們只是去拿拖把
We were just getting the mop.
你們要打掃什么的嗎
You gotta clean up or something?
差不多吧
Something like that.
你嗑嗨了嗎
Whoa, hey, are you stoned?
沒有  干什么
No, what?
你呢
Are you?
你在這里干什么
What are you doing here?
你是校鬼嗎
Are you the School Spirit?
什么  我剛剛結束籃球訓練
What? I just had basketball practice.
我只是來看看你是不是真的在留堂
I just came by to see if this was for real.
走吧  艾瑞卡  我們得去拿拖把了
Come on, Erica, we should go get the mop.
不  說真的  你嗑嗨了嗎
No, seriously, are you stoned?
這家伙逼你抽的嗎
Did this guy make you smoke?
什么  你說什么呢
What? How dare you?
沒人能逼我做任何事
No one makes me do anything.
好了  我們去走走
All right, well, let's go for a walk.
不行  我們得回去留堂
No, she can't, we have to get back to detention.
-她這樣子不行  -走吧  艾瑞卡
- Not like this she can't. - Come on, Erica,
我們真的該回去了
we really should get back now, okay?
沒事的  伙計
It's cool, bro.
好吧  我跟她可是一起很久了
Okay, we got a long history together.
非常非常久了
Way too much history together.
走吧  艾瑞卡
Let's go, Erica.
我們回頭圖書館見
I'll meet you back at the library.
我自己會走
I can walk!
這玩意真臭
That shit smells.
你覺得阿姆斯特朗真的要把我們都鎖起來嗎
You think Armstrong was serious about locking us in?
也許吧
Probably.
我先去我車上拿點東西
Let me get something from my car first.
我不懂了  誰盯著你們幾個
I don't understand, who's watching you guys?
阿姆斯特朗老師  但看來他是個酒鬼
Mr. Armstrong, but apparently he's an alcoholic.
別告訴別人
Don't tell anyone.
所以他給了你們大麻
So he's giving you guys weed.
不是
No.
No, no.
說來話長
It's a long story.
我們在哪
Where are we?
我不知道
I don't know.
我們就是玩玩
We're just chilling.
我正準備告訴全校人
So, I was just getting ready to tell everybody at school
我看到你周六來留堂了
I saw you here at Saturday detention,
但我打算給你個機會阻止我
but I was gonna give you a chance to stop me.
我告訴你個秘密吧
How about I tell you a secret?
說吧
Go on.
雖然我一整個夏天都躲你
Even though I ghosted you all summer,
我還是每11分鐘看一次你的主頁
I was still checking your profile every 11 minutes.
好吧
Okay.
這下我們有進展了
Now we're getting somewhere.
你什么意思
So, what are you saying?
我不知道
I don't know.
怎么了
What, what, what?
我好
I'm so...
怎么
Yeah?
嗨
...high.
我好嗨
I'm so high,
而且好餓
and really, really hungry.
好吧  那...
All right. Well, hey, hey.
我們回頭給你找東西吃
We'll feed you later.
不  我要去找自動販售機
No. I'm going to the vending machine.
現在嗎
Right now?
我要昏過去了
I'm going to pass out.
我馬上回來
I'll be right back.
那混蛋酒鬼把我們鎖起來了
That fucking drunk actually locked us in.
椒鹽餅  沒有嗎
Pretzels... maybe not.
薯片
Chips, chips, chips, chips.
巧克力  花生
Chocolate and peanuts.
那個不錯
That could be good.
好決定
That's a good call.
不錯
That's good.
誰想要一堆干果
Who wants a bunch of nuts?
巧克力
The chocolate.
那個不錯啊
That seems like that's the one.
好吧
All right.
好啦
Oh, there we go.
該死
Oh, shoot.
給我點時間
Just give me one second!
艾瑞卡
Erica?
Erica.
艾瑞卡  別鬧了
Erica, quit playing.
你是想報復我之前嚇唬你嗎
You just trying to get me back for scaring you earlier?
杰森·爾文自己控球
Jason Irving takes the ball himself.
他打斷了防守的腳踝
He breaks the ankle of the defender!
他又打斷了一個
He breaks another one!
誰去叫醫務人員
Somebody get a medic!
這怎么回事
What's this?
艾瑞卡·楊等在邊緣嗎
Erica Yang is waiting at the rim?
小心  艾瑞卡
Watch out, Erica.
你要被攔截了
You about to get crossed up!
搞什么
What the fuck?
杰森
Jason?
如果你是想嚇我
If you're trying to scare me,
我可以告訴你那很沒意思
I can tell you that's a turnoff.
這可不好玩
This isn't funny.
好吧  我給你兩分鐘
Okay, I'm going to give you two minutes
不出來我就回去留堂了
or I'm going back to detention.
我剛用廁紙清理過
I just cleaned it up with paper towels.
太好了
Fantastic.
艾瑞卡呢
Where's Erica?
你沒丟下她自己吧
You didn't just leave her by herself, did you?
她正嗨著呢
She's baked right now.
我不知道  她在自己玩呢
I don't know. She was doing her own thing.
那什么意思
What does that mean?
你沒見過艾瑞卡吧
You haven't seen Erica, have you?
沒有
Nope.
但阿姆斯特朗可把我們關在這里了
But Armstrong for sure locked us in.
好吧
All right.
我走了
I'm leaving.
杰森
Jason?
什么叫"她在自己玩呢"
What do you mean, "she's doing her own thing"?
我跟你說話呢
Hey, I'm talking to you.
你今天做的還不夠多嗎
Haven't you done enough for today?
如果你那么擔心她嗨大了
If you're so worried she's stoned,
你為什么要帶電子煙來
why did you bring the vape pen in the first place?
你什么毛病
The fuck is your problem, bro?
你把大家都拉低到了你的水平線
You're bringing everyone down to your level.
這讓你覺得不那么糟糕了嗎
Does it make you feel like less of a screw-up?
喂  別那么對她說話
Yo. Don't talk to her like that.
你不了解我
You don't know me.
你在這兒呢
There you are.
抱歉
Sorry.
我剛剛跟個朋友在一起
I was...with a friend.
這家伙企圖泡你了嗎
Did this guy try to make a move on you?
沒有
No.
我剛剛跟杰森在一起
I was...with Jason.
前男友
The ex-boyfriend!
你出現幻覺了嗎
Are you hallucinating?
因為樓里沒人
'Cause there's no one in the building.
已經封鎖了
It's locked.
那他肯定是在之前進來的吧
He must have gotten in beforehand, right?
嗯  我們本來在一起
Yeah. We were hanging out,
然后我離開了一下
and then I left for a second,
再回去時  他就不見了
and when I came back, he was gone.
他肯定在樓里
Well, he's gotta be here somewhere.
除非他被阿姆斯特朗逮到了
Unless Armstrong caught him.
那很奇怪
But that is really weird, 'cause...
因為拉斯也是突然就走了
Russ left without a word, too.
別那么多戲了
Stop being so dramatic.
他經常突然走人
He ditches all the time.
才不呢  我們在一起時不會
No he doesn't, not when we're together.
那學校鬼魂可能把他綁了起來
Okay, so then, the School Spirit probably has him chained up,
給他吸了一發  他可能正爽著呢
sucking him off. He's probably loving it right now.
哥們  為什么每次我想跟你說認真的事
Dude, why is it that every time I try to get serious with you,
你都自動說些蠢話
you automatically say something stupid
從不回答問題
and never fucking answer the question?
好奇怪  杰森居然那樣丟下我
It is really weird Jason would just ditch me like that.
你看到他了嗎
Did you see him?
我就拿了拖把然后回來了
I, uh, I just got the mop and came back here,
我以為你倆會想獨處
I assumed you guys wanted to be alone.
我們該告訴阿姆斯特朗老師嗎
Should we tell Mr. Armstrong?
說什么
For what?
他可能真逮到了誰
I mean, he probably did catch somebody,
只是不想出來
he's just staying low-key
因為這位預科生發現了他口里的酒氣
after preppy here called him out on his alcohol breath.
8月24日  星期六留堂細節
伊麗莎白·惠特莫爾
拉塞爾·瓊斯
小維·卡斯特羅  +8個星期六
布雷特·卡勒維
艾瑞卡·楊
好吧  聽著
Okay, look.
今天接下去的時間我們就待在這吧
Let's just stay in here for the rest of the day,
尤其是阿姆斯特朗老師已經醉了
especially if Mr. Armstrong's already drunk
而且發生了不少怪事
and weird things are happening.
沒發生什么怪事
Nothing weird is happening,
除了現在已過了午飯時間
other than it's past lunchtime
而那蠢貨還沒回來放我們休息
and that idiot isn't back yet to let us go on break.
不  我要去他辦公室拿我的手機
No, I'm gonna go grab my phone from his office.
也許我該跟你一起去找杰森
Maybe I should go with you and look for Jason.
我說話時到底有沒有人聽
Does anyone ever listen to me when I say stuff?
我們聽到你說的了
We hear what you're saying,
但你說的太沒勁兒
it's just that what you're saying sucks.
聽著
Look.
艾瑞卡不希望今天的事被人知道
Erica's trying to keep a low profile today,
學校又被封鎖了
and the school's on lockdown.
外面的一切看上去都很危險
Everything just seems dangerous out there.
老兄  我說的校鬼故事是鬧著玩的
Dude, I was playing around with the whole School Spirit stuff.
那個僵尸女老師是假的
The zombie teacher lady isn't real.
你現在變得像個膽小鬼  你知道嗎
You're starting to sound like a real pussy, you know?
是啊
Right.
你就勇敢了
And, what, you're the tough guy?
你說什么
What'd you say?
大聲點  你想讓別人聽到  我聽著呢
Speak up. You want people to listen, I'm listening.
各位
Guys!
我們沒時間吵架
We don't need this right now.
我承認我有點害怕
I can admit I'm a little scared.
也許還有點疑神疑鬼
Maybe I'm getting a little paranoid.
但我也知道你沒那么勇敢  維克多
But I also know you're not that tough, Victor.
你怎么不站起來當我面說
Why don't you stand up and say it to my face?
你可以肆意欺負我
You can bully me all you want.
我知道你為什么這么做
I know why you do it.
這話是什么意思
What the fuck is that supposed to mean?
起來
Get up!
歡迎回來  上將
你覺得自己比我強嗎
You think you're better than me?
你想見識下硬漢嗎
You wanna see a tough guy?
怎么回事
What is this?
維克多  坐下
Victor, sit your ass down.
我干什么了
What did I do?
去走廊站著
Out in the hallway.
我得打個電話
I need to make a phone call.
伊麗莎白  閉嘴
Elizabeth, shut your mouth.
拜托  我什么也沒做
Please, I didn't do anything!
等等  阿姆斯特朗先生
Wait! Mr. Armstrong!
我嗑藥的勁兒肯定過了
My high is definitely wearing off.
好了
All right.
我受夠了
I'm done with this shit.
我要找方法離開這里
I'm figuring out a way to get out of here.
老兄  你就不能冷靜會兒
Dude, can you just chill for one second?
我覺得我們該待在一起
I think we should stay together.
別誤會了  艾瑞卡·楊
Don't get it twisted, Erica Yang.
我們不是朋友
We're not friends.
我知道周一時
I know when Monday comes,
你還會一副不認識我的樣子
you're gonna act like you don't know me,
所以我打算按自己的想法辦事
so I'm gonna go do my own thing.
對了  別忘了
Oh, and don't forget.
我知道你今天留堂了
I know you were here today.
我知道你在留堂時嗑藥了
I know you got high in detention.
小維有自己麻煩
Vic has his own stuff.
他有時會這樣
He gets like this sometimes.
你覺得他會告訴別人嗎
You think he'll tell anyone?
不不  他不是這樣的人
No, no, he's not like that.
我覺得我們該去拿手機
I think we should go get our phones.
嗯
Yeah.
你跟布雷特怎么了
So what's up with you and Brett?
沒怎么
Nothing.
我今天剛認識他
I just met him today.
他很喜歡你
He's really into you.
他是個好人
He's a nice guy.
他看你時有那種迷戀  渴望的眼神
He's got that infatuated, yearning look when he sees you.
別假裝你沒注意到
Don't pretend you don't notice.
咱倆雖不一樣  但我們都是女孩
You and I are different, but we're both girls.
我知道你知道我知道布雷特喜歡你
I know you know that I know that Brett likes you.
你也可能喜歡他
And you like him too, probably.
那是什么
What the fuck is that?
姐們  你干什么  你去哪
Dude, what are you doing, where are you--
我們還是得拿手機
Shh! We still need our phones.
好吧
Okay.
布雷特
Brett?
阿姆斯特朗老師
Mr. Armstrong?
好吧
Okay.
阿姆斯特朗老師
我們是來拿手機
We're here to get our phones.
還有鑰匙
And the keys.
該死
Aww, shit!
媽的
Oh, fuck!
我沒見到我們手機或鑰匙
I don't see our phones or the keys.
不在他包理
It's not in his bag.
8月24日  留堂詳情
以下學生將在學期首周留堂
請注意新規定  由于赫布魯克高中失蹤學生數量增加
管理者務必時刻與學生在一起
維克多·卡斯特羅  破壞公物
拉塞爾·瓊斯  曠課
伊麗莎白·惠特莫爾  違抗命令
艾瑞卡·楊  作弊
你留堂是因為作弊
You're in detention for cheating?
什么
What?
你怎么知道
How do you know that?
在阿姆斯特朗老師的留堂郵件里寫著呢
It's on Armstrong's detention email.
這就是你的大秘密
That's your big secret?
失蹤人口  內森·列維
梅麗莎·凱斯
你知道
You know...
布雷特被阿姆斯特朗老師
Brett had this worried look on his face
帶走時臉上有種非常焦慮的表情
when Mr. Armstrong was taking him away.
就像他知道自己要遭遇不好的事了
Like he knew something bad was going to happen to him.
失蹤人口  邁克·斯萊特
杰茜卡·帕克
大衛·威爾遜
內森·列維
梅麗莎·凱斯
好吧
Okay.
那血  消失進墻里了
The blood. It disappears into the wall.
怎么了
What is happening?
這會我們該走了
This is when we get the fuck out of here.
所以是真的
So it's true.
確實有僵尸老師帶走壞學生
There's some zombie teacher lady taking bad students.
如果是真的  那阿姆斯特朗是什么角色
If that's true, then where does Armstrong fit in all this?
我們去找小維吧
Let's just find Vic.
那是...
Is that...
阿姆斯特朗老師
Mr. Armstrong?
是你嗎
Is that you?
你把杰森怎么了
What'd you do with Jason?
-拉斯在哪  -還有布雷特
- Where's Russ? - And Brett?
你不能把我們關在這里
You know you can't keep us here!
我們不是壞學生
We're not bad students!
學校這么爛也不是我們的錯
It's not our fault that this school sucks!
該死  跑  快點
Oh, shit. Run, go!
該死
Fuck!
Fuck.
對不起  我總是閉不上嘴
I'm sorry, I can just never keep my mouth shut.
回到學校
喂
Yo!
去這  去這
Okay, in here, in here.
好吧
Okay.
看  也沒那么傻
See? Not so dumb after all.
真不敢相信發生了這事
I can't believe this is happening.
我會永遠和這些聯系在一起
I'm forever going to be associated with this.
你知道嗎  我開始厭煩你的抱怨了
You know what? I'm getting really sick of you complaining.
你為什么這么在乎別人怎么想
Why do you care so much about what people think?
這里能出去嗎
Can we go out this way?
這里為什么有圍欄
Why are these bars here?
是為了防止我們出去還是不讓我們進來
Are they to keep us out or keep us in?
我們得離開這里
We need to get out of here.
我們不能一直躲在這里
We can't just hide here forever.
這是什么教室
What room are we in?
化學實驗室
The chemistry lab.
太好了  這樣我們就能做個炸彈之類的
Great. So we can, like, make a bomb or something.
他還在外面嗎
Is he still out there?
他們是不是說過
Didn't they say, like,
不要把什么東西和什么東西混在一起
don't mix something with something else,
否則后果很嚴重
or, like, it'd be really bad?
有硫酸嗎
Is there sulfuric acid?
上將隊
太蠢了
So dumb.
我一直以為我會是赫布魯克第一位
I always thought I'd be the first student from Helbrook
考上哈佛的學生
to make it to Harvard.
這個鬼地方沒人考上過哈佛嗎
No one from this hell hole has ever gone to Harvard?
沒有
Never.
這正是我每年都刻苦學習的原因
That's why I slaved away every year,
創造了想讀哈佛大學的愿望
created this whole Harvard-bound image,
和每個老師搞好關系  這樣就能拿到推薦信
sucked up to every teacher so I could get letters of recommendation.
其實...
Well...
并沒有結束
it isn't over.
我們要離開這里
We're getting out of this.
不
No.
都結束了
It's over.
我不會從赫布魯克拿到一封推薦信
I'm not getting any recommendations from Helbrook.
只是因為你作弊被抓嗎
Just 'cause you were caught cheating?
其實...
Well...
我真正想做的是賄賂阿姆斯特朗老師
what I actually tried to do was bribe Mr. Armstrong
讓他進入教務系統
to go into the system
把一堆A-改為A
and change a couple A-minuses I had to As
來得到最高的平均分
to get the max GPA.
我猜他會收下的
I guess I assumed he'd take it.
我猜錯了
I was wrong.
他還真是個正派的人
The guy actually cares.
如果我知道會發生這一切
If I knew all this was going to happen,
我就不會那么努力了
I wouldn't have tried so hard.
振作起來  老兄  你能行的
Come on, man, you fucking got this,
你能行的  別像個娘們似的
you got this, don't be a fucking pussy.
該死
Fuck this, man!
抱歉  我只想找到我的朋友
I'm-I'm sorry, I was just trying to find my friend.
不不不不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
你聽到了嗎
Do you hear that?
什么
What?
那是...
Is that...
有人求救嗎
someone calling for help?
是小維嗎
Is that Vic?
聲音是從哪里傳來的
Where's that coming from?
我覺得是從天花板上傳來的
I think it's coming from the ceiling.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
幫我一把
Help me up.
你瘋了嗎
Are you crazy?
如果那東西在上面呢
What if that thing's up there?
小維
Vic?
麗莎
Lizzy!
該死
Fuck.
聽我說  拜托  我不是...
Look, please, I'm not...
不  不
No, no!
麗莎
Lizzy!
不  不
No! No!
麗莎  不
Lizzy, no!
我要離開這里
I'm going out there.
-什么 -我去拉響火警
- What?  - I'm gonna--I'm gonna pull the fire alarm,
然后消防隊就會來救我們
and then the fire department will have to come and save us.
好吧
Okay.
小心點
Be careful.
好的
Okay.
開門
Hey, open up!
天啊  開門
Oh my god, open the door!
是布雷特嗎
Is that Brett?
拜托  阿姆斯特朗老師在外面  他瘋了
Please, Mr. Armstrong's out here, he's lost his mind.
小維和你在一起嗎
Is Vic with you?
沒有  我不知道  讓我進去好嗎
No, I don't know, just let me in, okay?
先去拉響火警
Go pull the fire alarm first.
你在干什么  為什么把我鎖在外面
What are you doing, why are you locking me out?
去拉響火警  你已經在外面了
Pull the fire alarm, you're already out there!
我不想死
I don't want to die!
艾瑞卡  拜托
Erica, please.
-讓他進來吧  -好吧  好吧
- Just let him in. - Okay, okay,
讓我把這東西放下來
just let me put this down.
好
Okay.
你還是要把門鎖上
You still have to lock the door.
我能鎖
I can do it.
小維在哪
Where's Vic?
你們知道小維關于校鬼沒說什么嗎
You know what Vic didn't mention about the School Spirit?
那個被學生丟在地下室
The old teacher the kids left to rot
任由其腐爛的老師
in the cellar on campus?
那是...
It's that...
她有個孩子
she had a son.
我就知道有點不對勁
I fucking knew something was up.
他的名字不在留堂名單里
His name wasn't on the detention list.
我想告訴你們大伙留在教室里
I was trying to tell you guys just to stay in the classroom.
我不理解你們為什么
I don't get why you guys can't just
就不能尊重赫布魯克
treat Helbrook with respect.
赫布魯克因為學生們的表現太差
You know, Helbrook doesn't receive the public funding it needs
所以收不到資助基金
because of the students' poor performance.
你們知道嗎
Did you know that?
但是  如果有學生能考上哈佛大學
Although, if someone were to get into Harvard...
這的確能改變現狀
that would really change things.
但當我聽到你作弊
But when I heard that you cheated,
我真的很失望
I was really disappointed.
還有賄賂  是怎么回事
And what was that, bribery?
艾瑞卡
Erica.
你是赫布魯克最棒的學生
You're Helbrook's greatest student.
年度最佳學生
The perfect Admiral.
告訴我這不是你干的
Tell me you didn't do that!
-布雷特  -告訴我你沒把事情搞砸
- Brett...  - Tell me you didn't screw it up.
告訴我你不是壞孩子之一
Tell me you're not just one of the bad kids.
告訴我
Tell me!
混帳東西
Hey, fuck face!
艾瑞卡
Erica?
Erica!
艾瑞卡
Erica?
Erica!
艾瑞卡
我在哪里
Where am I?
你醒了
Oh, hey.
抱歉  等一下
Sorry, just a moment.
抱歉我之前有些生氣
Sorry if I was a bit angry earlier.
今天真的很不順利
This day really didn't go well.
我媽媽警告過我
My mom warned me.
她教書的時候經常帶我來赫布魯克
She used to bring me to Helbrook when she was teaching.
她帶我來這里  為了讓我遠離那些壞孩子
She kept me in here to protect me from the bad kids.
我從小在家里受教育
I was homeschooled as a boy
但最后這里卻成了我的家
but ended up making this place my home.
這里很不錯吧
It's neat, isn't it?
今天早上  我很震驚
This morning, I was shocked.
我真是不敢相信我的眼睛
I... I couldn't believe my eyes.
艾瑞卡·楊  參加周末留堂
Erica Yang, weekend detention?
我本來只想袖手旁觀的  但后來我想
I was just gonna watch, but then I thought,
"還記得艾瑞卡說的嗎
"Hey, remember that thing Erica said?
"這是最后一年了
'It's the final year,
以后我們可能就見不到彼此了  所以
and after this, we may never see each other again, so...
不要留下遺憾"
let's not have any regrets.'"
我一直很想和你說上話
I always wanted to talk to you.
看
See?
赫布魯克的艾瑞卡·楊勇奪數學競賽冠軍
我真的很喜歡你的臉
I just love your face.
我從高一時就關注你了
I've been following you since freshman year.
赫布魯克的艾瑞卡·楊
自從你代表赫布魯克贏下了那次數學競賽
Ever since you won that math contest for Helbrook.
赫布魯克  艾瑞卡·楊
我和媽媽都很自豪
Mom and I were so proud.
你是我們最耀眼的明星
You're the brightest star we ever had.
你總是非常尊重和熱愛這所學校
You always treated the school with honor and respect,
這是我們最想要的
and that's all we wanted.
直到今天
Until today.
艾瑞卡
Erica.
你那么努力
You worked so hard!
我們都很支持你
We were all rooting for you,
你為什么背叛我們
why did you betray us?
我沒有
I didn't.
我犯了一個錯誤
I made a mistake.
肯定是他引誘你的  對嗎
Well, he must have tricked you, didn't he?
我想我是被壓力擊垮了
I guess the pressure was getting to me.
不  你不能向壓力屈服  艾瑞卡
No, you can't succumb to pressure, Erica!
特別是同輩壓力  好嗎
Especially peer pressure, okay?
比如說今天
Take today, for instance.
如果我沒有阻止拉斯
If I didn't stop Russ,
他就會讓你在校園里未成年喝酒
he was gonna get you to commit underage drinking on campus.
我無法阻止你抽煙
And I couldn't stop you from vaping,
但我阻止了杰森趁你在那種情況下
but I did stop Jason from taking your virginity
奪走你的童貞
while you were under the influence.
幸好我今天來了
Thank god I came today.
不然你這樣一個好女孩就被毀了
It would have ruined a good girl like you.
你真好
That's so sweet.
至少阿姆斯特朗先生不會再告訴任何人
At least Mr. Armstrong won't be telling anyone
關于你賄賂的事了
about your bribe, huh?
我一般不會干掉教職員
I don't usually remove faculty...
但是今天出現了一些額外情況
...but there were some extenuating circumstances today.
我去年和這些家伙一起留堂
I sat in detention with these guys last year
想要說服他們變好  但是
and tried to convince them to be good, but...
有的學生就是沒有希望
some students are just hopeless.
真不敢相信有人會這么在乎
I can't believe anyone cares so much.
我當然在乎了  我
Of course I care, I...
我希望有更多學生會在乎
I wish more students cared.
我同意
I agree.
謝謝你  布雷特  這么照顧我
Thank you, Brett, for looking out for me.
我很遺憾你住在天花板里
I'm sorry that you live in the cellar.
你肯定很孤單吧
It must get lonely.
我不介意
I don't mind it.
我今天和你一起真的很開心
I really had a nice time with you today.
我也是
I did as well.
真可惜
It's a shame.
我覺得我們真的很合得來
I felt like we were really getting along.
我其實也這么感覺
I felt that too, actually.
我覺得我們可以成為朋友的
I think we could have been friends.
一起出去玩  一起學習
Hung out, studied together.
也許我們可以
Maybe we could even have...
一起去舞會
gone to a dance together.
真的嗎
Really?
你參加過舞會嗎
Have you ever been to a dance?
沒有  我不能去  但是
No, I'm--I'm not allowed, but...
很棒吧
Isn't this nice?
是的
Yeah.
我只能經常自己想象
I have to use my imagination a lot.
你和我經常一起去參加舞會
You and I have gone to many dances together.
你現在不用想象了
Well, you don't have to use your imagination.
我就在這里
I'm right here.
我媽媽不希望我和這些學生交流
Well, my mom doesn't want me interacting with the students.
但我不是那些壞孩子
But I'm not one of the bad ones.
是我
It's me.
艾瑞卡·楊  年度最佳學生
Erica Yang, Admiral of the Year.
為了進入哈佛努力學習
Studied hard so I can get into Harvard.
好吧
Okay.
我能和你跳一支舞嗎
May I have this dance?
看
See?
你做得很不錯
You're good.
布雷特
Hey, Brett?
嗯
Yeah?
我知道你這些年來一直在
I know you've watched over the school
注視著這所學校
all of these years, and...
我知道你很懂好學生應該怎么做
...you're an expert on how students should be.
你可以這么說吧
I guess you could say that.
但是  你有沒有
But, do you ever...
想過你自己
...think about yourself?
你知道你最瘋狂的事是什么嗎
Want to know the craziest part about you?
你竟然認為我真的  真的會想和
That you think I would ever, ever want to dance
你這樣的瘋子跳舞
with a psycho like you.
你在開玩笑嗎
Are you fucking kidding me?
順便  我經常作弊
By the way, I cheat all the time.
我恨學校  但我還是很棒
I hate school, but I do well anyway
因為這對我來說生死攸關
because it is life or death for me.
你不了解我的父母  布雷特
You don't know my parents, Brett,
所以不要假裝你好像很了解我似的
so don't act like you know a thing about me.
媽媽
Mama...
還有一件事
One more thing:
我不是你的天使
I'm not your angel.
我和杰森做過27次了
I've had sex with Jason 27 times already,
我給三個不同的家伙口過
and I've given three different guys blow jobs.
我很抱歉
Sorry about it.
你在流血嗎
Are you bleeding?
-你受傷了嗎  -不
- Are you hurt? - No.
不  這不是我的血
No, it-- it's not mine.
你從哪里出來的
Where did you come from?
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
我叫艾瑞卡·楊
My name is Erica Yang.
我在留...
I was in det...
我在學校里進行我的周末社區服務
I was on campus for my weekly community service.
然后我聽到我的朋友們
And that's when I heard my friends
在樓里大喊救命
calling for help inside the building.
我就想去救他們
I tried to help them.
我盡力了
I did the best that I could.
伊麗莎白和我想盡辦法想逃出來
Elizabeth and I did our best to escape,
但我最終還是被一個精神病殺人狂抓住了
but I was ultimately held captive by a psychotic murderer.
就算在那一刻
Even in that moment,
我滿腦子里也只有
all I could think was,
"我那么努力才走到今天
"I've worked so hard to get here.
我快要完成我的哈佛申請了
I'm almost done with my Harvard application.
我不能掉鏈子
I can't get derailed.
求你了
Please.
不要讓我死"
Don't let me die."
但是
But...
我堅持了下來  活了下來
I persevered and I survived.
我覺得這次的經歷讓我更加的堅強
I think this whole experience has made me stronger.
現在  我已經開始繼續準備我的大學申請
And now, I've gotta get back to my college applications.
至少我現在的個人介紹有很多可以寫了
Hey, at least I've got one heck of a personal essay to write.